ellioskids.com 2014-10-07

# Privacy | Dr. Oetker

1\. Dr. Oetker North America Website  
This privacy policy is applicable to Dr. Oetker’s activities in North America and the Dr. Oetker North American web site located at [](http://www.oetker.ca/)[www.oetker.ca](http://www.oetker.ca/) (“the Website”) and may be different than the privacy policy posted at the Dr. Oetker’s international web site [](http://www.oetker.com/)[www.oetker.com](http://www.oetker.com/).

Visitors’ (“you”) use of the Website is subject to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In any case, by submitting personal information via an active information collection point on the Website, you specifically consent to the collection, use, and dissemination of such information in accordance with this privacy policy.

2\. Gathering and Using Your Personal Information

The only personal information that we will collect is the personal information that you knowingly provide to us when you communicate with us through the Website, or by any other means, such as submissions, contests and communications to the Website. No personal information is gathered without your consent. You always have the ability to refuse to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information.

When we do collect personal information, we use it only for the purposes described in this privacy policy or for the purpose indicated when it was collected (for example, consumers who write to us for free recipes will receive these recipes and we will not use their contact information for any other purposes).

In certain limited circumstances, we may be required or permitted by law to disclose your Personal Information, such as to the police in the course of a criminal investigation.

Personal Information collected on the Website belongs to [Dr. Oetker Limited] and may be transferred to a purchaser of all or some of [Dr. Oetker Limited’s] assets or business.

3\. Contact Us

If at any time it is unclear as to the reason we are requesting your information, or the purpose the information will be used for, or if you have questions, concerns, or complaints about your privacy or your personal information, you may contact us at the address listed below. We will inform you of our complaint procedures and will assist you in resolving the situation.

[Dr. Oetker Canada] can be contacted at [customer_service@oetker.ca](mailto:customer_service@oetker.ca).

4\. How We Care For Your Personal Information

We will not knowingly or deliberately forward your information to a third party without your consent or except as otherwise provided for in this privacy policy. This includes selling, leasing, or making your information available to a third party. If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post the changes here. However, if we make material changes to the way we use your personal information we will ask for your consent before we do so.

Please note that we work closely with a select group of third parties, such as marketing and promotional agencies or data processors, in order to facilitate the operation of the Website and to make the Website more enjoyable for visitors. Often, these third parties support programs and other activities related to the Website for which your personal information is required. As a result your personal information may be transferred to one or more such third parties for activities and processing relating to these purposes. Additionally, we ensure such third parties follow the same policies that we follow in order to guarantee the safety of your personal information.

At any time after you have submitted your personal information for whatever reason, if you wish to withdraw your consent for our use of such information you may do so subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If you withdraw your consent, we will inform you of the implications of such withdrawal; in some cases the withdrawal of consent may prevent us from providing you with goods or services in the future. To withdraw your consent, simply contact us and advise us of what personal information you no longer wish us to use. We will at any time, at your request, provide you with a copy of any personal information that we are holding about you.

[Dr. Oetker Limited] uses commercially reasonable steps to keep any personal information which it collects about you secure from unauthorized access, deletion or alteration, but, as with any communication of personal information over the Internet, there is a risk that data will be intercepted or otherwise interfered with by third parties. [Dr. Oetker Limited] will have no liability to you if your personal information is intercepted or otherwise interfered with by third parties. You should take precautions to ensure that your personal information is not accessed by others; such precautions include the use of passwords and encryption and turning off your computer when you are finished using it.

5\. What Is Personal Information

For the purposes of this privacy policy, “personal information” means “any information about an identifiable individual, and includes:

Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
Email Address  
Age  
Date of Birth  
Sex

6\. Gathering Information with Cookies

Cookies are used minimally on the Website. “Cookies” are small data files that are sent to your browser and then are placed on an individual visitor’s computer hard drive by a web server. Currently, with respect to the Website the 'Session ID' is the only thing stored in a cookie on a visitor’s computer. The purpose of this is to identify the user to the server while the visitor is browsing the Website. This function is not permanent; it only is valid while the visitor is on the Website. It will expire if the user jumps to another site and does come back in a short period of time, approximately 30 minutes. No information about the visitor, the visitor’s computer, or the visitor’s environment is saved by the Website in any way. If you do not want to accept cookies, you will often be able to prevent them from operating by changing your Internet browser settings. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will provide you with further information in this respect.
